Hey everyone! Have you ever heard of Frazee Grant?
Because this is a new brand I'm going to show you today
and I have two outfits.
They look a bit disarranged but I promise you when I'm going to wear them
they'll look so cool.
These are unique party leather outfits and
yeah obviously I've worn a black and a colorful one
and I'm going to change into the first one now.
First outfit.
Let me get rid of this.
In white and turquoise. I don't know how you pronounce it actually.
And I found matching shoes.
Because how cool is that that they have the same holographic parts than the bra here.
I put my hair up so you can see the shoulders better because I think it's a really cool
outfit and design and something kind of unique the whole outfit is super playful
and I paired it with some white fishnets and white pennies and super cute I
especially love the shoulder pads here and all the rivets everywhere like the
matching collar that is integrated into the bra and the harness strap here and
And this is basically just like a... not a skirt but a piblo part.
So yeah, I think you can also combine it maybe with a catsuit or with a different kind of outfit.
But this one would be my party version.
I had a photoshoot with Fuchs Teufelswil a while ago and we shot these outfits together.
She had a really cool sparkling hat I was wearing.
That is definitely an accessory to pimp these outfits. Totally recommend it.
And I have to say I haven't worn the black one so far.
So now is the time.
Let me change the black one.
And you know me of course.
I do prefer black.
I have to say the other one is also fun.
But this is my happy color.
And I love it.
I love the combination with the over knee boots I put under it.
And it's just a really cute outfit.
Again we have these shoulder parts here.
But also the chains here in the front and I think they're really cool
The white one had a integrated collar and I think that's something that's missing here like something for a neck
I mean I do have collars
Maybe this one my d20 collar
I think it kind of completes the look if you wear a collar I think this is a great fit too
so I could also wear something that has something dangling around here so to fill out the space a
more especially to maybe mirror the chains here from the skirt. So anyway
that's what I have on hand here and now you can decide for yourself who wore
better, Fuxi or me at this shoot. Anyway I think I am going to wear this one to a
fetish party in summer when it's nice and warm outside so I'm not going to
sweat and look great. Yeah festivals, fetish parties, queer events. These are
very great outfits for these kind of occasions. If you like these outfits
check out Phrasey Grand. I will put the Instagram link and the Etsy shop in the
description text and get your hands on something really cool and unique. I hope
you enjoyed this video. Leave a comment down below, thumbs up and subscribe to my
channel if you haven't already I will see you in the next video have a nice day bye